Class of 1928 Records, 1924-1993
Smith College Archives
Class of 1928 Records
1924-1993
Smith College. Class of 1928.
RG 80 UUID:7eb593b5-1039-48e8-a356-1c966fa10f2e
24 boxes (17.7 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1928.
The Class of 1928 was the fiftieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1928 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1928, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1928 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 4)
- Freshman Frolic 1924 (Box 1995, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1924-1925 (Box 1995, Folder 6)
- General undated (Box 1995, Folder 7)
- Groups 1924-1928, 1977 (Box 1995, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 12)
- Class Letters 1928-1987 (Box 1995, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Records 1955-1983 (Box 1995, Folder 14)
- Senior Dramatics 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1927 (Box 1995, Folder 16)
- Songs 1924-1928 (Box 1995, Folder 17)
- Sophomore Carnival 1926 (Box 1995, Folder 18)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1926 (Box 1995, Folder 19)
- Step Sings 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 20)
- Class Supper 1928 (Box 1995, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1929 (Box 1996, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1996, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1938-1943 (Box 1996, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1996, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 1996, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1996, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 1996, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 1996, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 1996, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 1996, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 1996, Folder 11)
- Reunion Costume (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook-A-F (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook-G-L (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook-M-Q (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook-R-Z (Box OV)